<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">“One of the Great, Great Insane Groups…”</string>
    <string name="article_title">Grateful Dead: Unlimited Devotion</string>
    <string name="article_text">“Come and join the party every day,”
        sang Jerry Garcia and his new band on their first original song, “The Golden Road to Unlimited Devotion”,
        on their first album, Grateful Dead. The party was in the Haight-Ashbury of San Francisco from 1965-1967,
        and in other zones of the Bay Area including Palo Alto and Berkeley (1963-1965), and Marin County (1968-1972).
        Over its career spanning three decades, the Dead would extend its repertoire to include many different musical idioms,
        and would bring its wild carnival and entourage to cities across America and Europe, but throughout it all, the band’s music would
        remain rooted in what was eventually called the “San Francisco Sound”.
\n\n
        The music of the Haight-Ashbury is special for me.
        I grew up in the Sixties, and some of these artists and musicians were my heroes,
        in the true meaning of the term. They stuck their necks out and literally risked their lives as well
        as livelihoods, to conjure up this music. None are more important to me than the Grateful Dead. Insanity incarnate,
        even graceful. In their philosophies, in their pursuits, and in every aspect of their lives,
        they embodied the spirit and the soul of the Hippie Generation of the Sixties.
\n\n
Since 1965, the Grateful Dead has been a focal point for acidheads and fringe lunatics, including
        geniuses, both inside and outside the counterculture. And while the Dead has a deserved
        reputation for putting out wildly psychedelic improvisational jams inspired in part by
        Thelonius Monk, Miles Davis, and John Coltrane, the band has always spoke with a distinctly
        Western American voice, distilled from American roots of folk, blues, bluegrass,
        and honky-tonk.</string>
</resources>